sup everyone can be faster with a very
special video today now I just woke up
maybe like two hours ago I just got done
watching Sonic Underground like I do
every morning after I get a bit
I got my cereal my own shoes and I
watched Sonic on the rag and then that's
when I realized something Sonic
Underground has the best opening of any
animated series ever in fact I realize
it was so good that I just had to make a
video explaining to people what this is
fact now you can put before saying you
gotta understand to fully enjoy sucking
on you need to watch the first 3 episode
before you watch any episode look for me
for example I make it like a ritual
light to do like what the first
three episodes at least before I watch
any show like foot I put be a fun one
any episode be flexible example if I'm
watching the exercise on country crosses
I make sure to say like a 12 to our like
time lining before I actually Upsy to
nature I can watch those three ABS
beforehand because the three answers if
you will be pulling your sock on
you gotta you gotta watch those three
episodes I didn't really get you they
merely make you feel like you're in the
water Sun on the ground and that the
characters are your friends and it
really feels if it feels like you're
truly alive
[Music]
put that window that's not what I up is
what the hell why those three episodes
son I'm not beginnings is the best
animated beginning to any animated
series ever now black when do I loads of
stuff the first episode epson 18 wait
there sorry but no other series has ever
done it starts off with with like them
as babies and that being separate
and throughout the whole episode you're
just watching them grow up I mean you
don't got this you don't get this kind
of connection to like all the other
piece of series do you know you
don't you just don't it doesn't roll
like that but that is how it goes down a
sock on the round cuz I got is gangsta
it ain't no it knows what's up it can do
things the other TV shows are afraid to
do you gotta respect that I'm I'm not
even kidding I ran into somebody just
the other day he told me quemas I
respect your opinion sure but talk about
it the fish chances aren't that good and
you know what I done you know what I
done I slap that I I beacon ass
cuz he doesn't know what's up I mean are
you kidding me me you mess with me
timbers one two three four five you say
it to me uh-uh no no it don't look that
bad when if you're if you're gonna say
this fuss Hawk arms after the out
I'm that good you're not you're not good
you need you stop you need to get your
priorities in order you need to you need
to know what's up plus I will get I will
get Knuckles the Echidna to be your ass
I mean I know Knuckles he will be yo ass
if you tried sucking down anyways
back to 0 saying what makes them so good
is the first day of the soccer really
get you connected to the characters like
no on the ceilings does like my episode
2 you get you see saw maggots on
Ukrainian left mastering the
weapons Manning and mastering his
drumsticks Sonic is mastering your super
speed because it's not like all the
cheese to Achilles train way through
series know the silent killers are war
do that war beating up on its
ass then making him the because
they want to get all the training
out of the way because the critters are
coming out they was mine up too no sock
Underground these characters they they
struck the gonna struggle throughout the
series baby to handle this baby give
your handle what's going what's going on
all the series no they don't do that but
soccer on does he know what's up what
why don't you get this I mean and why am
I the only one who gets this are
you stupid but really come on
it's not the hard to understand I mean
do you understand no push you down I do
though but what makes you see provide
the end of the first PFS you think down
he's sucking kicks there feel like my
family I mean you don't connect with the
main captivate you should like to do
with soccer man cuz it's good
Sonic on ram it in loves you just as
much as you love it you just got you
just go expecting more sadly some people
don't do that like me I mean that's
what's up the thing about the first day
of the up shut up I got a girl what's
most important in the first episode you
see a glimpse just just just a glimpse
of bowel be thou be the best character
in the series pika he only in there for
maybe 10 seconds but we own the why
because the Creator suck off they were
smiling up to know now we catch
up too much of Bobby we gotta keep the
goods we gotta keep the good for when
for wheat for when we can save our hand
because Bobby if you didn t minus x
you've all been only gonna go back to
the one episode but no you you gotta
have more Bobby to make you realize just
how good Saigon is that's why Bobby show
them why the series progresses because
he let's fake that Bobby's i'll give you
the main character I mean Sonic I'll
suppose upstairs he wants that ass but
ball the he oh my God I me Bobby hmm
Bobby is you it is the most beautiful
most badass most emotionally strong kept
in a series he walks Sonic he's crying
like a baby in the fellow Bobby mmm
fives up 37 Bobby the prison up better
of an episode of the seat by the way
Bobby a strong enough to go against
robotic and basically make the world his
he knows what
so anyways yeah Sonic on the brand has
the best beginning of any series ever if
you don't see this if you don't get this
way you're just wrong that's all the to
it if you don't believe me then I'll
just said it you're wrong you're wrong
haha I can't believe this you don't get
this do you well yeah is it you
can't argue with facts I mean try to
change save your mom's ain't gonna look
that way beginning the first three after
Sun on the ground it knows what it's
doing you don't